http://www.citizensadvice.org.uk/about-us/citizens-advice-privacy-policy/how-we-use-cookies/

Skip to navigation
Skip to content
Skip to footer
We use cookies to improve your experience of our website. You can find out more or opt-out from some cookies.
Coronavirus - being furloughed if you can’t work
Coronavirus - if you have problems getting your furlough pay
Coronavirus - if you're self-employed
Coronavirus - if you're worried about working
Coronavirus - if you need to be off work to care for someone
Complaining about social care services
What does it mean to have power of attorney?
Child abuse - advice and support
Advice for people affected by child abuse.
Top links
What health care can I get on the NHS?
NHS patients' rights
NHS Choices - Information on hospitals, conditions and treatments.
NHS and adult social care complaints
Find out how to complain about your doctor or health visitor.
England
This advice applies to England:
England home
Advice can vary depending on where you live.
Advice for other parts of the UK:
How we use cookies
When you use our website, we add cookies to your device to:
make sure the website works well for you - for example, remembering whether you want to see content for England, Wales, Scotland or Northern Ireland
find out how you're using our website so we can improve it
By using our website, we assume you agree to us adding cookies to your device. If you want to disable, block or remove cookies, you can do this at any time.
Remove or disable cookies
If you disable all cookies you:
won't be able to have your preferences remembered, like what country you live in
won't be able to fill in forms on our website
might not be able to use webchat or see content from other companies like Youtube videos or SurveyMonkey feedback forms
won't be able to log in - if you work or volunteer for Citizens Advice
To block cookies, you should change the settings in your web browser. You can also delete cookies that have already been set. Click on 'Help' in your web browser and search for 'cookies'.
Cookies from Google Analytics or Mouseflow tell us how you're using our site. You can opt out if you don't want these cookies added to your device.
Opt out from Google Analytics cookies.
Opt out from Mouseflow cookies.
You can find out more about cookies and how to delete them on the Information Commissioner's Office (ICO) website.
Making our website work well
We add cookies to your device so you have a good experience when you use our website - for example:
remembering your preferences
stopping the cookie notice showing all the time
making our online forms work
Remembering your preferences
This cookie remembers which part of the UK you prefer to view information in - England, Wales, Scotland or Northern Ireland.
This means you won't have to choose a location every time you visit our website.
Cookie nameHow long it's kept on your device
CABExtent
1 month
Stopping the cookie notice showing
This cookie stops the pop-up message about cookies showing on every page you visit - instead, it's only shown on the first 3 pages or until you close it.
Cookie nameHow long it's kept on your device
eprivacy
1 year
Making our online forms work
These cookies make our online forms work. They're put onto your device whether you use a form or not.
Cookie nameWhat it's used forHow long it's kept on your device
AWSELB
If you fill in a form on our website, this cookie makes sure the information is remembered so that it works when you submit it.
5 minutes
ASP.NET_SessionId
If you fill in a form on our website, this cookie makes sure the details you enter stay in the form while you're filling it in.
Until you leave our website by closing your browser
__AntiXsrfToken
This cookie makes sure form submissions on the website are from genuine users and aren't malicious.
Until you leave our website by closing your browser
Cookies other companies add to your device
If you use tools or services on our website that are delivered by other organisations, they might put cookies on your device when you use it.
The tools and services we have on our website from other organisations are:
Google forms, maps and Youtube videos - read Google's privacy policy
SurveyMonkey feedback forms - read SurveyMonkey's privacy policy
EventBrite events sign ups - read EventBrite's privacy policy
embedded Twitter feeds - read Twitter's cookies policy
videos through Vimeo - read Vimeo's privacy policy
embedded maps and presentations provided by Esri - read Esri's privacy policy
If you use online chat
When you use online chat, our chat provider LivePerson adds cookies to your device to make the chat work smoothly.
You can't be identified from any of the cookies and none of your personal information is taken through them.
Cookie nameWhat it's used forHow long it's kept on your device
LPSessionID / LPSID
This cookie remembers what you’ve done on our website including online chat.
Until you leave our website by closing your browser
LPVisitorID / LPVID
This cookie lets the system remember you when you come back.
2 years
Finding out how you use our website
We use tools called Google Analytics and Mouseflow to help us understand how you're using our website.
They collect information by putting cookies on your device. They share that data with us and we use it to improve our website - for example, making popular pages easier to find.
Google Analytics and Mouseflow collect information about:
your ISP and approximate ISP Location (City, Region, Country)
how you got to our website
The data collected through cookies is all anonymous - you can't be identified by it.We store the information for 6 months and then delete it.
Read more about how Google Analytics uses cookies.
Read more about how Mouseflow uses cookies in their privacy policy.
This cookies policy only covers citizensadvice.org.uk and its subdomains. Websites we link to should have their own cookies policy.
